A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, Program Files (Non-Grant), RG 5 FA1799
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Endowment Files, 1983-2015; 2; 27.53 Cubic Feet 72 letter document boxes and 1 half-letter box
  - Catholic Health and Rehabilitation Foundation, 87-7, 1987 March 27-1991 March 31 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Grant 87-7, Catholic Health and Rehabilitation Foundation, $250,000 for the endowment fund of the South Dade Catholic Nursing and Rehabilitation center, the income of which will be used to provide services to indigent clients.
  - City Center Ballet of San Jose, 90-143, 1990 June 19-1991 June 19 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Knight File Number - 1299
    Grant 90-143, $100,000.00, to establish a cash reserve fund. It will be used to alleviate cash flow problems, reduce interest expense, and provide seed money for the diversification of fundraising efforts.
  - Columbus Discovery Commemorative Fund, 87-273, 1987 December 15-1991 December 15 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Knight File Number - 1926
    Grant 87-273, $300,000.00, for endowment of the Greater Miami Opera and the Historical Association of Southern Florida and for capital needs of the Museum of Science and Space Transit Planetarium.
  - Duke University, 90-323, 1990 December 18-1991 December 18 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Knight File Number - 1213
    Grant 90-323, $1,000,000 to endow a Knight Chair in Journalism.
  - Florida Agricultural & Mechanical University Foundation, 90-325, 1990 December 18-1991 December 18 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 1221
    Grant 90-325, $1,000,000.00, for a Knight Chair in Journalism.
  - Foundation of the University of North Carolina at Charlotte, 90-108, 1990 June 19-1991 June 30 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 2366
    Grant 90-108, to the Foundation of the University of North Carolina at Charlotte for $333,000 to establish the Knight Distinguished Professorship of Business.
  - Health Education Center of Akron Inc., 90-123, 1990 June 19-1991 June 19 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 1372
    Grant 90-123, $10,000.00, for the endowment fund. 6/01/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT GRANT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - Hiram College, 90-47, 1990 March 20-1991 March 20 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 1376
    Grant 90-47, $10,000.00, to augment the Knight Foundation Scholarship Fund endowment and to match a grant from the GAR Foundation.
  - Historical Society of Pennsylvania, 90-201, 1990 September 27-1991 September 27 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 1377
    Grant 90-201, $50,000.00, to endow the graphics department and to match a challenge grant from the Andrew W. Mellon Foundation. 6/01/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT GRANT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - Hospice of Palm Beach County Inc., 90-6, 1990 March 20-1991 March 20 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Knight File Number - 1378
    Grant 90-6, $5,000.00, for an endowment fund. 6/01/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT GRANT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - Kansas University Endowment Association, 90-324, 1990 December 18-1991 December 18 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Knight File Number - 1402
    Grant 90-324, $1,000,000.00, to create a new chair in the William Allen White School of Journalism and Mass Communications to study the press, leadership and community.
  - Kent State University Foundation Inc., 90-24, 1990 March 20-1991 March 20 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 1403
    Grant 90-24, $1,000,000.00, to endow a chair for a professor to provide the expert counsel necessary to transform its current writing programs into a comprehensive system.
  - Mote Marine Laboratory Inc., 89-172, 1989 September 22-1991 September 30 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 1464
    Grant 89-172, $30,000.00, for an endowment campaign and to match a challenge grant. Mote Marine is an independent research institute dedicated to the advancement of marine and environmental sciences.
  - National Invention Center Inc., 88-132, 1988 June 30-1991 June 30 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 1476
    Grant 88-132, $800,000.00, a challenge grant for capital and endowment needs of the National Inventors Hall of Fame. Akron was chosen with the pitch "no place so well typifies the American spirit of innovation and business competitiveness as Akron, Ohio, in the heartland of the industrial revolution." Akron plans to make it a national monument to the American spirit of inventiveness and free enterprise and an educational center for students in Ohio and other nearby states.
  - Reporters Committee for Freedom of the Press, 90-22, 1990 March 20-1991 March 20 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 1779
    Grant 90-22, $100,000, for the Twentieth Anniversary Fund Drive. 8/16/11: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING SUPPORT. THIS GRANT WILL NOT BE INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT MANAGEMENT GOING FORWARD.
  - St. Vincent-St. Mary High School, 90-121, 1990 June 19-1991 June 19 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 1725
    Grant 90-121, $20,000.00, for a challenge grant to endow scholarships for minority, economically disadvantaged and handicapped students.
  - Victim Assistance Program, 89-113, 1989 June 21-1991 June 30 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Knight File Number - 1738
    Grant 89-113, $50,000.00, a challenge grant for the endowment of the Victim Assistance Program.
  - Alice Lloyd College, 91-237, 1990 September 27-1992 September 30 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Knight File Number - 5116
    Grant 91-237, $50,000, for the John S. Carroll scholarship endowment fund.
  - American Leadership Forum Silicon Valley Chapter, 90-155, 1990 September 27-1992 September 30 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Knight File Number - 1283
    Grant 90-155, $120,000.00, to sponsor four fellows a year for three years from the nonprofit and public sector.
  - Bellarmine College Prepatory, 91-314, 1991 December 12-1992 December 12 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Knight File Number - 5100
    Grant 91-314 to Bellarmine College Preparatory for $50,000 for the minority scholarship program and the minority recruitment program endowment fund.
  - Community Foundation of Santa Clara County, 91-282, 1991 September 19-1992 September 19 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 1314
    Grant 91-282, $1,050,000.00, for the Arts Fund, a collaborative stabilization campaign to benefit all the arts in Santa Clara County.
  - Community Hall Foundation, 91-74, 1991 March 26-1992 March 26 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 1199
    Grant 91-74, $40,000, for the Civic Theatre's programming endowment fund. 6/01/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT GRANT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - Epworth Village West Inc., 91-172, 1991 June 20-1992 June 20 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 1340
    Grant 91-172, $100,000.00, for the Good Samaritan Endowment Fund to support residential and medical care for elderly residents who have outlived their financial resources. 6/01/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT GRANT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - Florida Philharmonic Orchestra, 91-4, 1991 March 26-1992 March 26 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 1349
    Grant 91-4, $125,000.00, for general support and for the Endowment Fund to match a challenge grant from the National Endowment for the Arts. 6/1/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - Florida State University Foundation Inc., 91-265, 1991 September 19-1992 September 19 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 1343
    Grant 91-265, $50,000.00, toward an endowment to establish the Allen Morris Eminent Scholar Chair in Florida History. 6/01/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT GRANT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - Fredric R. Mann Music Center, 91-114, 1991 June 20-1992 June 20 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Knight File Number - 1359
    Grant 91-114, $15,000.00, to establish an endowment fund for the Mann Music Center, which provides a summer home for the Philadelphia Orchestra and other concerts in Fairmont Park. Its contribution to the overall attractiveness of the Philadelphia region and specifically to maintaining the world's largest city park as a place that residents and others want to visit is significant. 6/1/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - Guthrie Theater Foundation, 91-197, 1991 September 19-1992 September 19 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Knight File Number - 1367
    Grant 91-197, $25,000.00, for an endowment to support the Duluth and St. Paul segments of the Guthrie Young People's Fund. 6/1/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - Memorial Medical Center Foundation, 91-75, 1991 March 26-1992 March 26 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Knight File Number - 1435
    Grant 91-75, $63,000 for the renovation and endowment of the Child Protection Center. To provide a single place where the physical, psychological and social assessment of the victims of child abuse could be made. 6/1/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - New World School of the Arts, 91-64, 1991 March 26-1992 March 26 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Knight File Number - 1480
    Grant 91-64, $150,000.00, for the endowed scholarship program. To be able to offer students scholarships which cover not only tuition but also room and board. Promotes both higher education and art with the same dollars. NWSA is one of the best performing and visual arts high schools in the country. The college program is known as the Juilliard of the South.
  - Philadelphia Schools Collaborative, 91-294, 1991 December 12-1992 December 12 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Knight File Number - 2367
    Grant 91-294 to the Philadelphia Schools Collaborative for $100,000 for an endowment for the Philadelphia Scholars Fund and its program of "last dollar" scholarships for needy college-bound students.
  - School of Journalism Foundation of North Carolina, 91-378, 1991 December 12-1992 December 12 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 1718
    Grant 91-378, $1,007,000.00, to endow a Knight Chair in Journalism. The focus would be basic research regarding the future of mass communications in the U.S., especially newspapers.
  - Stanford University, 91-323, 1991 December 12-1992 December 12 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 1727
    Grant 91-323, $175,000.00, to continue the Knight Latin American Fellowship program.
  - University of Florida Foundation Inc., 91-372, 1991 December 12-1992 December 12 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 3028
    Grant 91-372, $852,000 for continuation of the Knight Minority program.
  - University of Notre Dame, 91-309, 1991 December 12-1992 December 12 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 4156
    Grant 91-309, $250,000 for an endowment for the Hesburgh Program in Public Service.
  - Variety Audio Foundation, 91-195 (Books Aloud), 1991 September 19-1992 September 19 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 1736
    Grant 91-195, $27,000.00, for the endowment of "Books Aloud," a reading by listening program for the blind and physically disabled. 6/1/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - Walker Art Center, 91-256, 1991 September 19-1992 September 19 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Knight File Number - 1760
    Grant 91-256, $250,000.00, for "The Fund for the Walker" capital campaign the major resource for contemporary art in the Upper Midwest and one of the premier contemporary art institutions in the country.
  - White-Williams Foundation, 91-101, 1991 June 20-1992 June 20 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 2368
    Grant 91-101, to the White-Williams Foundation for $10,000 for the endowment fund. 6/01/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT GRANT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - Balboa Art Conservation Center, 92-57, 1992 March 25-1993 March 25 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 1287
    Grant 92-57, $25,000.00, for an endowment fund for conservation training, graduate fellowships, staff development, research and publications.
  - Conservation Center for Art and Historic Artifacts, 92-60, 1992 March 25-1993 March 25 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 1321
    Grant 92-60, $25,000.00, for an endowment for conservation training, graduate fellowships, staff development, research and publications for four regional conservation centers. 6/01/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT GRANT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - Cornell University, 92-333, 1992 December 15-1993 December 15 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 1201
    Grant 92-333, $620,921, to endow the directorship of the Writing in the Majors Program in the John S. Knight Writing Program.
  - Curtis Institute of Music, 92-69, 1992 June 17-1993 June 17 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 1325
    Grant 92-69, $100,000.00, to endow a chair in the Symphony Orchestra of the Curtis Institute of Music. 6/1/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - ETV Endowment of South Carolina, 92-30, 1992 March 25-1993 March 25 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Knight File Number - 1215
    Grant 92-30, $150,000.00, for a capital campaign and to match an NEA challenge grant. South Carolina Educational Television, a public broadcast system, to improve education by sending programs into 93 percent of the state's public schools, reaching 83 percent of its students, the highest percentage in the nation.
  - Fort Wayne Museum of Art, 92-278, 1992 December 15-1993 December 15 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Knight File Number - 1356
    Grant 92-278, $50,000.00, for an endowment campaign to stabilize its base of operating support.
  - Intermuseum Conservation Association, 92-58, 1992 March 25-1993 March 25 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Knight File Number - 1383
    Grant 92-58, $25,000.00, for an endowment fund for conservation training, graduate fellowships, staff development, research and publications.
  - John and Mable Ringling Museum of Art Foundation, 92-62, 1992 June 17-1993 June 17 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Knight File Number - 1395
    Grant 92-62, $50,000.00, for the endowment campaign to match a grant from the NEA which they received in 1989 in the amount of $100,000.00 to be matched 3:1 over three years. 6/1/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - Johnson C. Smith University, 92-122, 1992 June 17-1993 June 17 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Knight File Number - 5101
    Grant 92-122, to Johnson C. Smith University, $1,000,000 for the capital campaign.
  - Michigan State University, 92-298, 1992 December 15-1993 December 15 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 1448
    Grant 92-298, $1,000,000.00, to endow a Knight Chair in Journalism. The focus of the Knight Chair in Journalism would be on environmental journalism. The environment has become a topic of enormous public interest, yet there is a significant gap between journalists and scientists resulting in an often uninformed public. This chair seeks to close the gap by forging a partnership between the School of Journalism and the MSU Institute of Environmental Toxicology, which engages in research, education and outreach activities centered around the environment.
  - Salvation Army (Southern Territorial Headquarters), 92-109, 1992 June 17-1993 June 17 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 1800
    Grant 92-109, $150,000, for the scholarship endowment fund for the School for Officers' Training.
  - Tuesday Musical Club, 92-74, 1992 June 17-1993 June 17 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 1730
    Grant 92-74, $25,000.00, to increase the endowment of the Clara I. Knight Fund.
  - University of Minnesota-Duluth, 92-176, 1992 September 16-1993 September 16 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 1798
    Grant 92-176, $50,000, for the Tweed Museum of Art's New Century endowment campaign.
  - University of South Carolina Educational Foundation, 92-239, 1992 December 15-1993 December 15 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 1731
    Grant 92-239, $30,000.00, for the endowment of the I. DeQuincey Newman Professorship at the College of Social Work. 6/01/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT GRANT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - Upper Midwest Conservation Association, 92-59, 1992 March 25-1993 March 25 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Knight File Number - 1735
    Grant 92-59, $25,000.00, for an endowment for conservation training, graduate fellowships, staff development, research and publications. 6/01/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT GRANT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - White House Endowment Fund, 92-244, 1992 December 15-1993 December 15 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Knight File Number - 1743
    Grant 92-244, $150,000.00, for an endowment to maintain The White House collection and public rooms.
  - Washington Drama Society Inc., 92-168, 1992 September 16-1993 September 16 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Knight File Number - 1762
    Grant 92-168, $50,000, to support the Allen Lee Hughes Fellowship Program, a cultural diversity program (a national model).
  - We Will Rebuild Inc., 92-223, 1992 September 16-1993 September 16 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Knight File Number - 1765
    Grant 92-223, $2,500,000, to support rebuilding South Dade County following Hurricane Andrew and for creating affordable housing for low-income residents.
  - Broward Performing Arts Foundation, Fort Lauderdale, 93-23, 1993 March 22-1994 March 22 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 1294
    Grant 93-23, $150,000.00, for an endowment campaign to provide a financial anchor for general operations and to establish designated special programs.
  - California Community Foundation, 93-357, 1993 December 14-1994 December 14 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 1295
    Grant 93-357, $250,000.00, to establish a donor-advised fund.
  - Central Carolina Community Foundation, Inc., 93-348, 1993 December 14-1994 December 14 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 1297
    Grant 93-348, $250,000.00, to establish a donor-advised fund.
  - Children's Home of Detroit, 93-40, 1993 March 22-1994 March 22 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 1304
    Grant 93-40, $150,000.00, for an endowment for a new chemical dependency program comprised of three components: prevention, assessment and continuing care. 6/01/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT GRANT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - College Assistance Program (CAP) of Dade County, 93-88, 1993 June 15-1994 June 15 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 1194
    Grant 93-88, $250,000, for endowment and operating support over three years.
  - Community Foundation for Southeastern Michigan, 93-352, 1993 December 14-1994 December 14 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Knight File Number - 1313
    Grant 93-352, $250,000.00, to supplement an existing donor-advised fund.
  - Community Foundation of Santa Clara County, 93-350, 1993 December 14-1994 December 14 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 1315
    Grant 93-350, $250,000.00, for the establishment of a donor-advised fund.
  - Dade Community Foundation, (now The Miami Foundation, Inc.), 93-345, 1993 December 14-1994 December 14 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 1329
    Grant 93-345, The Miami Foundation, Inc. $250,000.00, to supplement the donor-advised fund established in 1988.
  - Duluth-Superior Area Community Foundation, 93-351, 1993 December 14-1994 December 14 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 1335
    Grant 93-351, $250,000.00, to establish a donor-advised fund.
  - Endowment Fund of Lake County Inc., 93-299, 1993 December 14-1994 December 14 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 1337
    Grant 93-299, $10,000.00, for general operating support. For promotion, brochures, direct mail, and meetings with CPA's, attorneys, and estate planners to explain the many benefits of the foundation. 6/01/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT GRANT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - ETV Endowment of South Carolina, 93-72, 1993 March 22-1994 March 22 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 1216
    Grant 93-72, $95,000.00, for two-hours of "Firing Line with William F. Buckley" programming to be taped in conjunction with Knight Foundation grant dissemination conference for liberal arts colleges in June 1993.
  - Florida West Coast Symphony Inc., 93-26, 1993 March 22-1994 March 22 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Knight File Number - 1353
    Grant 93-26, $25,000.00, for the FUND FOR THE FUTURE, Endowment Campaign.
  - Foundation for the Carolinas, 93-353, 1993 December 14-1994 December 14 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Knight File Number - 1360
    Grant 93-353, $250,000.00, to supplement the donor-advised fund established in 1988.
  - Fort Wayne Community Foundation, 93-347, 1993 December 14-1994 December 14 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Knight File Number - 1354
    Grant 93-347, $250,000.00, to establish a donor-advised fund.
  - Fort Wayne Philharmonic Orchestra Inc., 93-256, 1993 December 14-1994 December 14 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 1357
    Grant 93-256, $50,000.00, for the endowment fund to assure the orchestra's financial stability.
  - Founders Society Detroit Institute of Arts, 93-154, 1993 June 15-1994 June 15 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 1361
    Grant 93-154, $1,000,000.00, for the Partnership for Renewal campaign to create an enhanced operating fund and to match a Kresge Foundation challenge grant to build the endowment.
  - Indiana Institute of Technology Inc., 93-97, 1993 June 15-1994 June 15 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 1384
    Grant 93-97, $20,000.00, to endow a Knight Foundation Scholarship Fund for minority students.
  - Long Beach Symphony Association, 93-49, 1993 March 22-1994 March 22 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 1422
    Grant 93-49, $50,000.00, for a challenge grant to stimulate an endowment campaign and for campaign expenses. 6/1/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 89-75, 1989 March 21-1994 March 31 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 1432
    Grant 89-75, $5,000,000.00, for a challenge grant to endow the Knight Science Journalism Fellowships.
  - Mississippi Museum of Art Inc., 93-24, 1993 March 22-1994 March 22 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 1454
    Grant 93-24, $20,000.00, for an endowment to support the Gulf Coast/Biloxi component of the Satellite Gallery Program. The goal is to enrich the cultural life of the Gulf Coast, where 25 percent of the population lives in proverty, by providing a rich array of high-caliber visual arts and education programs.
  - Phenix City Education Foundation Inc., 93-95, 1993 June 15-1994 June 15 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 1784
    Grant 93-95, $15,000, for an endowment to support enrichment activities for students in the local public schools.